quicklypopular.com 2016-11-03

# Privacy Policy - Quickly Poular

We at File Creator LTD. (“ **The Company** “, “ **we** ” or “ **our** “) put great efforts into making sure that your personal information is safe and used properly.

This policy explains our privacy practices for processing personal information on The Company’s online websites (the “ **Service** “). This policy applies to the use of The Company’s websites and it is an integral part of The Company’s [Terms of Service](http://quicklypopular.com/terms-of-use/ "Terms").

The summary of this policy will give you a quick and clear overview of our practices. Please take the time to read our full policy, which follows the summary.

Please contact us at: info@quicklypopular.com for further information, or if you believe that any content or activity on the Service violates this policy or your privacy.

**A Summary of the Our Privacy Policy**

**The Identifiable Information That You Provide Us –** We may request your valid email address to register and log-in. If you log-in with your social network’s account (for example, Facebook), we will indicate the basic details we will need.

**The Identifiable Information That We Collect** – We automatically log ‘traffic/session’ information including IP addresses, your Service sessions metrics and geographic location.

**The Identifiable Information That You Upload and Generate on the Service** – We may allow you to upload content to the Service, Your uploaded and generated data may include personal information. Please use caution and do not upload personal information of others without their consent.

**What Do We Do With Identifiable Information?** – We use the data to provide, maintain and develop the Service, to enhance your experience of the Service, and to protect us and the Service from misuse and law violations.

**Sharing information with others –** We may share information with our providers and affiliates to provide the Service, for advertising purposes subject to providing you an opt-out option, and if we change our corporate structure.

**Aggregated and Analytical Information –** Aggregated data is not identifiable. We use it for legitimate business purposes and may use standard analytical tools.

**Your Choice –** You may opt-out of our mailing lists, delete your account, and use the Service anonymously or as a guest.

**Data retention –** We retain data as needed, to provide the Service and for legitimate and lawful purposes.

**Transfer of data outside your territory –** We may store and process information in various sites throughout the globe, including in sites operated and maintained by cloud based providers.

**Cookies** – We use cookies to make it easier for you to log-in and to run and develop the Service.

**Information Security –** We implement systems, applications and procedures to secure your personal information, to minimize the risks of theft, damage, loss of information, or unauthorized access or use of information.

**Changes to this Privacy Policy** – We may update our policy from time to time after giving proper notice. **  
**

**Privacy Policy**

**The Identifiable Information That You Provide**

When you register with the Service through our website at: quicklypopular.com, or through any of our registration interface, we will ask you to provide a valid email address and to select a password. From time to time, we may add or change the personal information we request for registering to the Service.

If we ask for more than your email address, we will explicitly indicate the fields which are mandatory to complete. If you register with your social network’s account (for example, your Facebook account), we will indicate the details we will request and keep.

We may allow you to add additional information to your Service profile, including your name, location, and birth date. Note that your profile details may be publicly accessible on the Service, subject to your privacy preferences, as may be offered by us on the Service.

Additionally, when you contact us, or when we contact you, we may receive and process any personal information that you provide us.

**The Identifiable Information That We Collect**

When you access the Service, our servers log certain ‘traffic/session’ information from your device, such as the location of your device (city, region and country) and the Internet Protocol (IP) address that your device uses to access the internet when using the Service.

We will collect information about your Service activity, for example your log-in and log-out time, the duration of your sessions and other activity measures, and we will record the sites and webpages that you visit while logged-into the Service.

**The Identifiable Information That You Upload** **and Generate on the Service**

You may be able to upload content to the Service from your device and other resources, including from your account on social networks. The content you upload to the Service, including any data, text, graphics, audio and audio-visual files, may include personal information and may be accessible to other users of the Service.

Please use caution when uploading the content and avoid any involuntary disclosure of your personal information or disclosure of others’ personal information without their explicit consent.

We may remove any content from the Service, at our sole discretion or at a third party’s request, if we believe that the content violates the privacy, or good will of any person.

**Our Use of Your Identifiable Information**

We may use the personal information we collect and receive to provide our Service to you and to other users, to enable the Service tools and features, to study and analyze the functionality of the Service and users’ activities, and enhance users’ experience on the Service.

We may also use personal information to match content and features on the Service to your and other users’ preferences and activities, to provide support, to conduct surveys and send questionnaires, to maintain the Service and to continue developing the Service.

We may use your email address to contact you when necessary, to send you messages and to provide you information and notices about the Service. We may include commercial and marketing information in our messages.

We obey the law and expect you to do the same. We may use your identifiable information to enforce our[Terms of Use](http://quicklypopular.com/terms-of-use/ "Terms"), policies and legal agreements, comply with court orders and warrants, assist law enforcement agencies, prevent or stop unlawful activities such as fraud and identity theft, and take action in any legal dispute and proceeding.

**Sharing Identifiable Information with Others**

We do not share your personally identifiable information without your explicit consent, or provided that we maintain your ability to opt-out of the information sharing when we share your information with our third party affiliates for the purpose of serving you ads which correspond with your online activities and preferences.

We may share your identifiable information with the Service providers and other third parties, if necessary to fulfill the purposes for collecting the information.

We may also share personally identifiable information with companies or organizations connected, or affiliated with us, such as subsidiaries, sister-companies and parent companies, with the express provision that their use of such information will comply with this policy.

Additionally, a merger, acquisition or any other structural change may require us to transfer your personal information to another entity, provided that the receiving entity will comply with this policy.

**Aggregated and Analytical Information**

We may use standard analytics tools. The privacy practices of these tools are subject to their own privacy policies and they may use their own cookies to provide their services (for further information about cookies, please see the ‘Cookies’ section in this policy).

We use Google Analytics. For further information about how Google uses your personal information, please refer to: [www.google.com/policies/privacy/partners/](http://www.google.com/policies/privacy/partners/).

We use anonymous, statistical or aggregated information and may share it with our partners for legitimate business purposes. It has no effect on your privacy, because we have no reasonable way to extract data from the aggregated information that can be associated with you.

**Your Choice**  
At any time, you may unsubscribe from our mailing lists or newsletters by using the ‘unsubscribe’ option in our messages.

You may deactivate our third party cookies through <http://www.criteo.com/privacy/>. Note that if you disable the display of personalized ads from our third party partners, you will continue to receive ads that are less relevant to your interests and browsing behavior.

Some web browsers offer a “Do Not Track” (“DNT”) signal. A DNT signal is a HTTP header field indicating your preference for tracking your activities on the Service or through cross-site user tracking. The Service does not respond to DNT signals.

**Periods of Time for Keeping Information (Data Retention)**  
We may retain different types of information for different periods, depending on the purposes for processing the information, our legitimate business purposes as well as pursuant to legal requirements under the applicable law.

For example, we may need to keep certain information for tax related requirements, record keeping, archiving and legal issues.

We may keep aggregated non-identifiable information without limitation, and to the extent reasonable we will delete or de-identify potentially identifiable information when we no longer need to process the information.

In any case, as long as you use the Service we will keep information about you, unless We are required by law to delete it, or if we decide to remove it at our discretion.

**Transfer of data outside your territory**

The Service is web-based. We may store and process information in various sites throughout the globe, including in sites operated and maintained by cloud based service providers.

If you are a resident in a jurisdiction where transfer of your personal information to another jurisdiction requires your consent, then you provide us your express and unambiguous consent to such transfer.

**Cookies**

Cookies are packets of information sent to your web browser and then sent back by the browser each time it accesses the server that sent the cookie. Some cookies are removed when you close your browser session. These are the “Session Cookies”. Some last for longer periods and are called “Persistent Cookies”.

We may use Persistent Cookies to remember your log-in details and make it easier for you to log-in the next time you access the Service. We may use cookies for additional purposes, to facilitate the use of the Service’s features and tools and to display personalized advertisements in your future navigation.

Our Service allows services who provide online advertising services (“Ad-Serving Providers”) to display to you and other users personalized content and advertisements on the Service and on other online sites and services.

The Ad-Serving Providers use their own cookies and other technologies, such as pixel tags to collect and use personal information for displaying personalized ads, by them and by additional providers, and to run, maintain, measure the effectiveness and develop their services.

A pixel tag (also known as “action tag” and “web beacon”) is a 1X1 pixels transparent object which is embedded in a web page to enable the display of optimized content and advertisements to end users.

The use of these technologies by these advertising services is subject to their own privacy policies and is not covered by our Privacy Policy. We require our Ad-Serving Providers to include on the ads a link to information about their privacy practices and how to opt-out of their services. At any time, you may contact us at: info@quicklypopular.com and we will assist you in locating the Ad-Serving Providers’ privacy related information.

Every browser allows you to manage your cookies preferences. Please bear in mind that disabling cookies may complicate or even prevent you from using the Service.

**Keeping Your Information Safe**

We and our hosting services implement reasonable measures to secure your personal information, to minimize the risks of theft, damage, loss of information, or unauthorized access or use of information.

We make efforts to protect your privacy, but we cannot guarantee that the Service will be immune from any wrongdoings, malfunctions, unlawful interceptions or access, or other kinds of abuse and misuse.

**Changes to this Privacy Policy**

From time to time, we may update this policy. If the updates have minor if any consequences, they will take effect 7 days after we post a notice on the Service’s homepage, or send our users an email notice. Substantial changes will be effective 30 days after our notice was initially posted or sent.

Until the new policy takes effect, you can choose not to accept it and terminate your use of the Service. Continuing to use the Service after the new policy takes effect means that you agree to the new policy. Note that if we need to adapt the policy to legal requirements, the new policy will become effective immediately or as required.

**Incorporation to the Terms of Use**

This policy is an integral part of the Service [Terms of Use.](http://quicklypopular.com/terms-of-use/)

**Last updated: 15th of Sep  2015**
